So, whaddya want from us this time?
Here's the thing. From what I've been told,
the baron will paying us a visit next month.
The baron himself?!
More like the clown who thinks it's cool
to just demand 20 boars from us.
He's expressed interest in observing
your boar hunts firsthand.
Great. First he wants more boars, now he wants
a show. Will the surprises never stop?
Well, that's fine with me.
But why ask Allen to join us?
Let me explain. We need someone to serve
as a tour guide for the baron during his stay.
Huh?
You want me?
Why not just have your own son do it?
My Pelomas isn't suited to the task, I'm afraid.
You can say that again.
I'm hoping Allen can help us
show the baron hospitality starting with dinner
the night before the hunt.
So, basically, he wants me to entertain
the big cheese while he's in town.
And he's trying to win me over
with these molmo fruits.
Sorry, pal. But I ain't that cheap!
I've heard it was Allen's clever ideas
that led to the success of your hunts last year.
I'm sure he can handle this important job.
What do you say, Allen?
Frankly, I couldn't care less about the baron.
But I won't get any chances
to leave the village as a serf.
And it'll take 10 years of hunting boars and
albaherons before I can reach commoner status...
You can refuse if you want, okay?
If I remember right, there was one more ticket
to rising the social ladder...
The baron can gift people with commoner status.
Alright, then.
It's okay, Dad. I'll be the baron's tour guide!
EPISODE 6: OUTWARD BOUND
Welcome! We're honored
to have you, Baron Granvelle.
Thanks for the warm welcome.
Of course!
Come, Cecil.
Okay.
Chief Deboji. I appreciate the work that you've
put in over the years to establish Krena Village.
It's been 15 years since
the Land Reclamation Decree.
And there has been no greater success
than here in the Granvelle fiefdom.
Thank you, milord.
Also, I must apologize
for all the fuss over boar meat.
I knew asking for more would burden you unduly.
But I simply could not refuse an order
from His Majesty.
F-f-from the King, you say?!
Technically speaking, yes.
But the blame truly lies with Viscount Carnel.
That scoundrel!
Calling attention to the boar hunts
while we're in front of the King!
Milord. Your tone is frightening the chieftain.
My God! Exquisite!
Father! This meat is quite delicious!
What kind of meat is this, Chief Deboji?
Huh? Oh, um, well...
If I may interrupt, this is a dish of albaheron.
The meat is from one hunted just yesterday.
Only the freshest ingredients for you, milord.
It uses the breast meat, thigh meat,
and liver, all flavored with a blend of herbs.
Ah, I see.
Is this your son, Chief Deboji?
No, actually. This is the son of Rodin, one of...
Oh! Rodin the Boar Hunter's son, eh?
Now I remember why your black hair
and eyes seem familiar.
It's good to see you again, Sir Zenof.
I will be serving as your guide
during tomorrow's hunt.
Such a well-mannered young man.
Is his father a former member of the knighthood?
No, milord. He comes from a family of serfs.
Serfs?! You let one of them into your guest hall?!
Cecil! You know that serfs
are fair members of our fiefdom.
Don't treat them like some kind of animal.
Right. I'm very sorry, Father.
Why do I get the stink eye?
Son of Rodin.
I hope you're ready to acquaint us
on the finer details during tomorrow's hunt.
Yes. Of course, sir.
Wrangling 20 boars in one year is a steep goal.
Should it prove too difficult,
then my knights will take over the hunts.
Uh-huh.
Not convinced we serfs have what it takes, are ya?
That would be most wonderful, Zenof!
I asked my father to let me tag along
because I wanted to see a great boar up close,
but seeing the knights slay
one would be even better!
Sure.
Once you've shown them the fundamentals,
the knights can handle
the responsibility of hunting.
I beg your pardon, milord.
But 20 boars is a paltry number.
Huh?!
We will have no problems meeting the quota.
Our performance tomorrow
should convince you of that.
Zenof. I'm leaving Cecil under your protection.
I expect you to keep her safe.
Of course, my lord. It shall be done.
This is so exciting, Sebas!
Indeed, milady.
Here we are. You'll be able to see
all of today's action from atop this watchtower.
Please head on up.
Hmph!
Wow, what a great view!
Indeed. Trees as far as the eye can see.
This is the forest where the great boars nest.
The hunters have arrived.
Ah, I see they've got armor!
We made good use of the boars from last year.
That armor was forged
from leftover pelts, bones, and fangs.
I was asked to thank you
for granting permission, milord.
On behalf of my father, Rodin.
Okay, let's move out!
What are they doing?
Their job is to lure boars
into the hunting grounds.
Speed is a key factor,
so they are only lightly equipped.
Huh.
Please be patient as it may take time to lure
the boars, despite how many live in the forest.
Fair enough.
That reminds me, Allen.
How is the Sword Lord, Krena, fairing these days?
Ah, she's doing great!
Wonderful.
Let her know a tutor will be dispatched
here the spring after next to help her study
for the Academy entrance exam.
Understood.
It's hard to imagine Krena studying for anything.
She's gonna look so silly!
Here comes the first one!
Heads up!
Heave-ho!
As you can see, we start by boxing them in.
Those large shields are made from two layers
of the toughest part of the boar hide,
found on its back.
Strike team, you're up!
Long spear team!
The long spear team consists of the least
experienced members, who just joined last year.
The frontliners with the toughest job
are the ones wearing armor, I see.
Yes. It also covers their backs to prevent injury
if one of the long spear team misses the target.
The boar's neck is the best place to strike.
That was a fatal blow.
Ugh...
Wow. Most impressive.
Milady! Milady!
These men may not be knights, Your Lordship,
but I believe they are worthy
of being called warriors.
Yes, I must applaud their fighting prowess.
It seems there will be no problem with-
Incoming!
Two boars at once?!
Leibrand, make ready to assist!
Yessir!
Please wait.
There is no need to panic.
The hunting team is trained to deal
with these situations.
But even so!
Please let them handle it.
Stick to your training and split into two groups!
Gerda and I will take the lead! Move out!
Every hunter worth their salt
knows to kill all the game they bait.
Letting anything escape is folly.
But for the past 10 years, my dad
and the other serfs haven't been able to do that.
Mainly due to their lack of armor.
Sixty percent of their hard-earned
boar meat gets taken as tax.
And they have to exchange
the rest for daily necessities.
Spears were the only thing
they could afford to upgrade.
However, it's possible for them
to create some leeway by mastering
the most efficient hunting strategy.
That allows for gradual equipment upgrades,
which then raises their efficiency even higher.
It's the most basic of basics!
Milady!
Not again!
That's three boars down. All's going well!
Thank God. Watching them fight two at once
still has me sweating bullets.
That leaves 17 more to go.
No, milord. Just 10, actually.
Really?!
Seven boars had already been hunted this year
before you graced us with your presence.
I imagine we'll have filled the quota
by this time next month!
You don't say!
Doesn't seem like my knights
will be needed, after all.
Thank you. My father and the others
will be happy to hear it.
If I may, we actually have two requests
to make of you, milord.
Is that so? What are they?
For starters, we humbly ask for permission
to make two more of the shield walls.
In the interest of hunting
even more next year, I assume?
Exactly.
Very well. What else?
Secondly, we want to procure goods
not available in the village.
Specifically... liquor.
Liquor?
We would like your permission to trade in liquor
and allow its distribution among the serfs.
But what for?
As more and more boars are hunted,
there is a real concern that the
resulting abundance of meat
will reduce its value in the village.
Exchanging the meat for imported liquor
instead will help to prevent a market crash.
Why liquor specifically?
Given his position, this something
that Sir Zenof may understand better, but...
the hunters must risk their lives to be effective.
I get it. You need the liquor
to help keep their morale high, yes?
Precisely.
That's how my father explained it to me.
Your Lordship. I am of the mind
that their request stands to very good reason.
Then I shall consider it favorably.
Allen, was it?
I must say, you have done a splendid job today.
Thank you, milord.
Hey, you!
You were lucky to get any praise from my father!
Don't let it go to your head!
I mean, you barely even...
Careful, milady!
Hmph!
Let us be on our way, milady.
Yeesh. Talk about a delicate damsel.
Go back to your cushy city life.
That's probably the last I see of her.
Rodin. Gerda.
Yessir!
You've truly shown me what you're capable of.
I must commend your amazing hunting skills.
Your accomplishments deserve to be rewarded.
I wouldn't make a good baron otherwise.
Aw, yeah! Now you're talking!
Don't bother with money!
We want social mobility, baby! Come on commoner!
Rodin. Gerda. I hereby elevate you
and your families... to commoner status!
I expect that you'll continue to work hard.
Yessir! Thank you very much!
Thank you, milord!
HELL YES!
Goodbye serfdom! Hello commoner status!
Now I can go hunting outside the village limits!
I've dreamed about this moment
countless times over the past eight years!
My first stop: the White Dragon Mountains
to go dragon hunting!
For any serfs who have taken part
in the hunts for over 10 years,
I shall also grant the same status.
Do a thorough check and determine
who among your team are eligible.
Yessir!
I foresee no problems
fulfilling His Majesty's order.
Now I can return to the city and rest easy.
Milord.
What is it?
I believe there was one more thing
His Majesty was keen to know.
Ah! I nearly forgot!
His Majesty wishes to promote Krena Village
as a shining example for the rest of the kingdom.
Thus, he asked me for the details
of how the boar hunts began.
Y-you want to know the history behind it?
I haven't heard that story, myself.
That's actually a sore subject
for Rodin, Your Lordship.
May I tell it in his stead?
By all means.
It all started in spring... 13 years ago...
THE HARDCORE GAMER DOMINATES
IN ANOTHER WORLD WITH GARBAGE BALANCING
About 100 serfs from nearby villages
relocated here to help develop the land
as part of the Reclamation Decree.
After six months of hard work,
we had cleared out a good chunk of the forest.
Fall was on the horizon when disaster struck.
A great boar came out of nowhere and attacked us,
devouring most of the wheat and potatoes
that we had set aside for winter.
The majority of serfs had chosen
to brave the frontier
after struggling to obtain food
in their old villages.
Which meant going back wasn't an option.
That's when Rodin spoke up.
He proposed we hunt the boars for meat.
Back then, we didn't have any of the weapons,
armor, or knowledge that we do now.
In spite of that, all the men united to go hunting
with pickaxes and hoes as weapons,
and we managed to kill a single boar.
That sounds like a story to pride yourself on.
You came together to accomplish a difficult task.
The problem is... we lost a friend in the process.
After defeating the boar, we overcame
a Trial of the Gods and our injuries were healed.
But our friend wasn't as fortunate.
I've told Rodin over and over again
that he shouldn't blame himself,
but he just won't hear it.
So that's it.
Now I understand why Dad
covered for that commoner.
It's because he once lost a friend the same way.
Hrm. I'm sorry to dredge up such a painful memory.
That's okay.
But listen, Rodin. Although lives were lost,
the village could never have come this far
without your prudent actions.
Let me honor the bravery of your youth
with one more reward.
Ask of me whatever you wish.
Huh?!
Oh, sweet! That triggered a bonus event!
A nice cherry on top before we wrap this up!
Congratulations, Dad! Ask him for some liquor!
Well, Baron Granvelle... I do have one request.
Would you please allow my son
to work at your estate?
Huh?!
Allen has a better head
on his shoulders than I do.
Any job is fine, even just hallboy.
I promise that he'll be an asset!
Huh? Wait.
No! Bad idea, Dad!
That is not what I had in mind!
It... it could ruin everything!
Hmm. Work at my estate, eh?
Sebas?
I have no problems with it.
He seems plenty clever to me.
Say no, dammit!
Let me live my dream of hunting legendary dragons!
I'll have even LESS freedom living with the baron!
G-g-g-gotta think. Must be a way outta this.
A hallboy, eh? No, that won't do.
Crap, crap, crap. Please don't...
Allen, son of Rodin.
I hereby appoint you...
as manservant of the Granvelle Family.
WHAT?!
M-manservant?! Really, milord?!
You can't be serious, Father!
Just the idea of having a serf
in our house makes me sick!
He is a commoner now, milady.
How are hallboy and manservant any different?!
Wait, forget that!
I need to get myself out of this mess!
Think! Come up with some excuse!
Allen!
I look forward to serving you, milord...
Damn. There's just no way I can turn it down.
I'm boned.
All set. It looks great on you, Allen.
Thanks, Mom.
Aw, Allen. You really gotta go?
Yeah. Take care of yourself, Krena.
Hey, Krena. How about one more duel before I go?
Yay!
I am Krena the Fierce! Have at thee!
I am Allen, manservant to Baron Granvelle!
Sword Lord Krena! Do your worst!
Here I come!
What a good way for them to say goodbye.
That's for sure.
Tugs at the heartstrings.
What's going on?
Whoa, is Allen... overpowering Krena?!
I used nearly all the magic stones that I
had stocked up and created 20 copies of Hawkins.
I went all in on agility!
When Krena turns 12,
she'll leave to study in Academy City.
Then she'll go into the royal service.
It's possible we'll never see each other again.
Did I just lose...?
Sword Lord Krena.
I think we can both agree that this was a draw.
It was?
We'll settle this in the future,
when we meet again!
Okay! I'm gonna win for sure, Allen!
Now there's the smile I wanted to see.
Allen.
Take care not to get sick, okay?
Okay.
No more tears, Mash.
You have to step up to protect Mom and Myulla now!
Hey. Say goodbye to Myulla, too.
Myulla. Grow up nice and big, okay?
I still remember helping deliver you
as a baby, kiddo. It makes me sad to see you go.
Shucks, Miss Mathilda. Thank you.
Stay safe, Allen.
I will.
Thanks for everything!
Hey, don't push me.
Aw, crap!
Dogora?
And Pelomas?
Uh, hi.
Here.
It's for me?
Hmph! Don't say I never gave you nothin'!
That kid's a riot!
And generous to boot!
Yeah!
Let's get going, Allen.
Right.
Allen.
Manservant is only the first step for you.
Work hard and you'll go places.
Yeah. I'll do my best!
Hey! They're almost ready to leave!
Bye, son. Make me proud.
Come home if it gets too tough, okay?
Goodbye, everybody.